Sorry for a moment.
ちょっとごめん
I got angry.
怒られちゃったな
No way.
まさか
Aren't you filming?
撮ってるんじゃないの?
Because I came all the way.
せっかく来たから
already.
もう
It’s your first time, right?
初めてでしょ?
first time.
初めて
I heard you read manga.
漫画読むとこって聞いてたんだけどな
I don't read manga, right now.
漫画読んでないね、今んとこ
I don't read it anymore.
もう読んでないよ
Hey, hey, what?
ちょ、ちょ、あれ?
what?
何?
It's a life-killer.
生殺しじゃん
Because.
だって
Well, that's it.
ちゃうでしょ、あれは
You said no, right?
だめって言ったでしょ?
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
What are you doing?
何 してんの?
何してんの?
What are you doing?
何 してんの?
What are you doing with your hands?
人の手を使って何をしてんの?
a little bit.
ちょっと
There's nothing I can do.
何 もできないんだよな
I can't stand it.
我慢できないじゃないし
It all ended in a good place.
だんだんいいとこで終わっちゃった
I can't help it.
しょうがない
Clerk?
店員さん?
The staff came.
スタッフさんが来ちゃった
Mr. Hasegawa?
長谷川さん?
lie?
嘘?
Did you see the name?
名前見てたの?
This is really bad.
めっちゃダメだね、これ
what?
何?
Why?
何で?
Can I take it off?
脱いでいいの?
I.
僕
It's okay to take it off.
脱いで大丈夫
Because I want to see it.
私見たいから
please.
お願い
Once you take it off, it will go away.
脱いだらもう解消される
I said it.
言ったね
I can't help it.
しょうがないな
thank you.
ありがとう
That's cute.
それ可愛いね
Cute belt.
ベルト可愛い
belt?
ベルト?
What did you think?
何だと思ったの?
necklace.
ネックレス
If this were a necklace, it would be pretty cool.
これネックレスだったらだいぶイカつい
Something like this?
こういうこと?
oh yeah.
そうそう
Must be strong.
強いといけない
Red suits you.
赤似合うね
I might not wear it that often.
そんなにあんま着ないかも
It suits you.
似合う
Because it's peace.
ピースだから
I can't help it.
しょうがない
It's been a while since we last met.
久 しぶりにあったからね
It's been a really long time.
めっちゃ久しぶりだよね
Not though.
ないけど
not at all.
全然
Will you wait?
待ってくれるの
mosquito?
か?
It's over.
終 わった
It's early.
早いよ
Early, early.
早 い早い
Don't make too much noise.
声だらだ出さないで
Mr. Hasegawa is coming.
長谷川さん来ちゃうから
I felt really awkward when I went home.
帰るときめちゃくちゃ気まずくなっちゃったじゃん
Possibly Pokkishi.
ぽっきしで多分
That clerk is Pokkishi.
あの店員さんぽっきしだ
I'm not stupid.
バカじゃないよ
What is this?
これ何?
what?
何ですか?
This is terrible.
やばいよ
I'm fluent.
ペラペラしてる
Even just the top.
上だけでも
She has a really nice body.
めっちゃいい体してる
Move.
動いて
sorry.
ごめん